addthis.us 2019-04-06

# BEZH INTERNATIONAL | Privacy Policy :: Bezh privacy policy

BEZH: EU reg nr: DK36165510 

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?  
  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, social security number or other details to help you with your experience.  
  
When do we collect information?  
  
We Do not collect your information if you do not use the followings: when you register on our site, place an order, fill out a form Shopping online or enter information on our site. Using any of the followings, is considered as giving us the full rights to save your information, however we still have no data saved in our servers and we will not have.  
  
How do we use your information?  
  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:  
  
      • To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.  
      • To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.  
      • To quickly process your transactions.  
  
How do we protect visitor information?  
  
Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.  
  
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. ( https://www.bezh.com )  
  
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.  
  
For your convenience we may store your credit card information longer than 30 days in order to expedite future orders, and to automate the billing process.  
  
Do we use 'cookies'?  
  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.  
  
We use cookies to:  
      • Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.  
      • Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.  
  
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  
  
If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won't affect the users experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.  
  
However, you can still place orders .  

Third Party Disclosure  
  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.  
  
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
  
Third party links  
  
We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.

BITCOIN?  

If you are paying for any of our products or services using Bitcoin, or if you are trading Bitcoins through our brokers (Bitcoinmoney.dk), all the risks are on your side. Bitcoin is Not safe. It is not trackable and will not be subject to any disputes in any court. It means that it is your risk to do Bitcoin business with us and we accept no responsibility if your Bitcoin gets Hacked, Lost, Stolen or disappeared by any of our services, products or websites. If you do not agree with these conditions, then please do not use our Bitcoin solutions.  

Google  
  
We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.  
  
According to Danish law, we agree to the following:  
Users can visit our site anonymously  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.  
  
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:  
      • On our Privacy Policy Page  
Users are able to change their personal information:  
      • By chatting with us or sending us a ticket  
  
How does our site handle do not track signals?  
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.  
  
Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?  
It's also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking  
  
Fair Information Practices  
  
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.  
  
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
We will notify the users via in site notification  
      • Within 7 business days  
  
We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.  
  
Contacting Us  
  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  
  
BEZH General Trading, BEZH.COM  
European Registration Number: DK36165510   
Copenhagen 2300  
Denmark
